He made her his star. And his darkest obsession.
The Girl is a drama, tv movie film directed by Julian Jarrold.
Director Alfred Hitchcock is revered as one of the greatest
creative minds in the history of cinema.
Known for his psychological thrillers, Hitchcock’s leading
ladies were cool, beautiful and preferably blonde.
One such actress was Tippi Hedren, an unknown fashion model given her big
break when Hitchcock’s wife saw her on a TV commercial.
Brought to Universal Studios, Hedren was shocked when the director, at the peak of his
career, quickly cast her to star in his next feature, 1963’s The Birds.
Little did Hedren know that as ambitious and terrifying as the production would be to shoot,
the most daunting aspect of the film ended up coming from behind the camera.
Tippi Hedren, played by Sienna Miller.
Alfred Hitchcock, played by Toby Jones.
Alma Reville Hitchcock, played by Imelda Staunton.
Evan Hunter, played by Conrad Kemp.
Peggy Robertson, played by Penelope Wilton.
Melanie, played by Angelina Ingpen.
Call Girl is a 2012 political thriller film directed by Mikael Marcimain
and written by Marietta von Hausswolff von Baumgarten.
It stars Sofia Karemyr, Simon J.
Berger and Josefin Asplund.
The story is a fictionalised version of events based on the so-called Bordellhärvan political scandal of 1970s
Sweden which linked several prominent politicians to a prostitution ring that included underage girls.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.